Pontus Sundén

Project Manager

Stängselgatan 9 417 16 Göteborg 070 549 3773 pontus@psu.se

SKILLS

I'm an experienced project manager working with both large and small projects. Also strong skills in web development and IT-management. I have a good understanding of the developer and the technical side as well as the business perspective. My background is in web and marketing, with about 10 years in the higher education industry.

EXPERIENCE

Multiple referrals are given on request.

University of Gothenburg – *Project Manager*

APRIL 2017 - PRESENT

- Development of digital course and academics catalog.
- Groundbreaking use of PIM system in the higher education industry.

University of Gothenburg – *Team Leader*

APRIL 2016 - MARCH 2017 (1 yr)

- Team leader for a small communications unit.
- Responsibilities including day-to-day management, strategy and participate in recruitment.

Sahlgrenska Academy, University of Gothenburg – Communications Officer

OCTOBER 2014 - JANUARY 2019 (4.5 yrs)

- Digital marketing, social media, graphic design and web development.
- Placement at Sahlgrenska Academy, the medical faculty.

University of Gothenburg – Communications Officer

OCTOBER 2011 - OCTOBER 2014 (4 yrs)

- Work within IA/UX, web design and usability testing.
- Additional tasks within project management, employee training and system support.

Pontus Sundén Media – Owner

2002 - 2013 (12 yrs)

- Web development and graphic design for non-profits and indie artists.
- Technics including PHP, HTML/Javascript/CSS/Json.

Fässbergsgymnasiet, Mölndals stad – Teacher in Social Sciences

2010 - 2011 (2 yrs)

Foab Systems AB, Göteborg – Electrician

2003 - 2005 (3 yrs)

EDUCATION

University of Gothenburg - Master of Education

2005 - 2011 (5 yrs)

- Subjects: Math and Social Studies
- Special interest in the governance of education and use of digital tools in education.

ADDITIONAL

Languages

Fluent in written and spoken Swedish (native) and English.

Certifications

Certified Scrum Product Owner (Scrum Alliance)

Software and environments

Basic knowledge in programming

Fluent in Adobe Creative Cloud

Fluent in Microsoft Office, specifically Excel

Familiar with *nix environments

Other

Driving license